Contact

zoro41111@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ mohamed-184526201 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Data Analysis
Data Science
Data Visualization

Certifications

What is Deep Learning
Become a Data Analyst
Tableau Essential Training (2020.1)
Excel Statistics Essential Training: 1
Demystifying AI/ML/DL

Mohamed Mostafa

Data Analyst at Freelancer.com

Summary

I m engineering graduate with passion for solving the problems in data analyses ,i work in data analysis projects ,I made a lot of project in Data analysis (gathering-Assess-visualize) ,I have experience also in Quality management .I face a lot of problems in my life but this problems gave me a big experience in my life ,I have a good skills in data analysis using python script I'm ready now to help you.

Experience

AD

Technical Manager engineer January 2018 - Present (4 years) Cairo, Egypt

- I m a Technical manger engineer in AD company.
- I am a leader of the Technical engineer group.
- We improved the performance of the company and increase the profit by 30% annually.

MTC

System Engineer
July 2004 - Present (17 years 6 months)
Cairo, Egypt

- 1- I made the the quality management plan to improve the sequence of work.
- 2- I did 3 training courses for the quality engineer in the company.

WS#60

Technical Engineer
July 2006 - December 2017 (11 years 6 months)
Cairo, Egypt

- I made the data analysis for the last 5 years in WS#60
- I visualized and reported the results to know what is the situation of the work trajectory.

Education

Udacity

Nano degree program , Data analyess · (2021 - 2021)

Udacity

Nano degree program, Data Anayses · (2020 - 2020)

Ain Shams University

Master of Engineering - MEng, Rf and microwave design · (2013 - 2017)

MTC

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Electrical, Electronics and Communications Engineering \cdot (1999 - 2004)